# **Efren Medina**

Cell: 317-987-5553 Email: efrenmedina@live.com Linkedin - <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/efren-medina/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/efren-medina/</a>
Portfolio - <a href="https://efrenmedina1.github.io/">https://efrenmedina1.github.io/</a>
Github - <a href="https://github.com/efrenmedina1">https://github.com/efrenmedina1</a>

**Summary:** Recent graduate of Salesforce Pathfinder program and Eleven Fifty JavaScript Bootcamp. Providing six years of Human Resource and Property Management experience, I bring strong analytic and communication skills to find and provide solutions.

## **Skills and Highlights:**

JavaScript - HTML5 - CSS3 - React.js - PostgresSQL - Angular - Express - Certified Salesforce Admin - Apex - Visualforce - Aura - Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, Power Point, Outlook,) - WMS - ADP - Kronos - Prolaint - Paylocity - Workday - Trello

## JavaScript Projects - 2019

**Dog Paws App PEAN** - Team group project to make a website for the selling, breeding, and sharing of dogs. Users are given a social media platform where they can make a profile, chat on a forum, and upload dogs. https://dogbreedproject.herokuapp.com/

**Kickboxing Instructor Website PEAN** - Full stack website using Angular and Node.js. It is the Kickboxing Instructor's personal website where he will advertise himself and interact with his clients.

https://marcusverdeflorhaynes.herokuapp.com/

**Pokemon Team App PERN** - Website using PERN (Postgres, Express, React, and Node.js). Used Pokemon database API along with my own database. Use a Pokedex to create a Pokemon team. <a href="https://efrens-pokemon-client.herokuapp.com/">https://efrens-pokemon-client.herokuapp.com/</a>

**Studio Ghibli App** - Made a website utilizing an API to display information through JavaScript, HTML, and CSS.

https://efren-studio-ghibli-api.firebaseapp.com/

**Javascript Website** - Made a website with uniform navigation bars and pages that teaches JavaScript. https://efrenmedina1.github.io/Tutorial-Webpage/

## **Work Experience:**

## Recruiter - Sep 2019 to Current

Adecco Staffing

Process candidates for client's peak hiring season and newly created distribution center. Interview, background check and administer drug test to candidates.

#### Seasonal Human Resource Specialist - Sep 2018 to Nov 2018

Ascena Retail Group

Three month contract to onboard over 1000 employees. Primary responsibility included interviewing over 30 candidates a day, phone screening candidates, and advertising job posting.

#### **Human Resource Specialist - Mar 2013 to Aug 2018**

Readerlink Marketing Services

Handled day to day Human Resource activities for a distribution warehouse of 250 employees. Interview candidates for positions in the warehouse and provided new hire and benefit orientation. Acted as a backup for managers and supervisors in times of absence. Was selected to go on a five week business trip to help start operations of a new warehouse as a project manager.

#### Inventory Control Clerk - June 2011 to Mar 2013

Readerlink Marketing Services

Managed department's inventory on the warehouse database. Displayed initiative and developed operation process that improving production.

#### Real Estate Manager - Aug 2013 to Current

Self-Owned Business

Property owner of three houses that I currently lease. Maintains and negotiates contracts with tenants, as well as contract renovations to be made on properties.

#### **Education:**

Salesforce Pathfinder Program
June 2019 - Aug 2019
Indianapolis, IN
Certified Salesforce Administration

Eleven Fifty Academy Jan 2019 - Mar 2019 Fishers, IN JavaScript Ivy Tech Community College 2010 - 2011 Indianapolis, IN Computer Science